

PERSONAL INFORMATION

I have a 1.5 year's experience in studying and developing personal and commercial projects in JavaScript/React/React Native/Redux. I'm also briefly acquainted with jQuery.

My main aim is to become a highly qualified specialist in the field of commercial projects development.

REWARDS AND CERTIFICATES

- First place in the "game design" nomination at the *Ludum Dare* gaming hackathon
- *Udemy* certificate at the end of the paid HTML and CSS course
- *Udemy* certificate at the end of the paid JavaScript and React/Redux libraries course
- *Udemy* certificate at the end of a paid course of advanced study of JavaScript and the React library
- Imaguru certificate of successful completion of the program of creation of one's own business
- Certificate of successful completion of an internship at MVP connect

CONTACTS

Phone: +375296269141 Email: shpoisnik@gmail.com Telegram: @shponik

SOCIAL MEDIA





NIKITA SHALIMO

Frontend developer (Junior)

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Consulting services for the preparation and performing of course projects on the subject "Computer network hardware"

December 2020 - May 2022

Management and preparation of trainings in various fields of activity (design, copywriting, management, financial analysis)

April 2022 - June 2022

Internship at MVP connect

July 2022 - September 2022

Participation in two commercial projects. Front-end development (JavaScript, React, React Native). Layout using Figma, work with various APIs, work with Firebase, implementation of front-end and back-end communication.

EDUCATION

Belarusian State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics

Bachelor Degree, the Faculty of Computer Systems and Networks, specialty of Computing machines, Systems and Networks" | 2017 -2021.

PERSONAL QUALITIES

Purposeful, conscientious, hard-working, friendly, responsible, sociable.

SKILLS

- HTML5/CSS3/SCSS
- JavaScript/React/React Native/Redux
- Webpack/Gulp
- AJAX (Fetch API/XMLHttpRequest/Axios)
- Working with various APIs
- Git/GitHub
- Scrum
- Windows, Linux, MacOS
- Experience in working with relational databases

ENGLISH INTERMEDIATE

Intermediate level B1

MY PORTFOLIO

Click me